Guide to the Cornell University songs and sheet music, 1870-2000.
Cornell University songs and sheet music, 1870-2000.
- Series III. Song Booklets
  - Cornell University Songs, 1881; 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Includes: Alma Mater, The Broken Chord, Bonunkus, Bull-Dog, Cold Day When We Get Left, Chapeau, Cascadilla, The Chimes, Cornell Version, Cornell, Class Song '72, Class Song '73, Class Song '80, Class Song '83, Clementine, Cocachelunk, Children, Hail! Hail! Hail!, Crow Song, Drinking Song, Doloroso, Days In Bivouac, Down In Old Kentucky, Evening Song At Cornell, Eighty-Three Song, Founder's Hymn, Fourteen Long Weeks In A Pris-i-on, The Girls Of Ithaca, Good Old Cornell Times, Gospel Train Am Coming, The Hour Is Late, Hard-Up, Hark I Hear A Voice, I Wish I Were Single Again, Junior Supper Song, Junior Exhibition, Keep Me From Sinking Down, King Of The Cannibal Islands, Litoria, Landlord, Fill Your Flowing Bowl, Moustache, Mermaid, My Little Dog, O'er Hill And Dale, Parting Song - Class Of '72, Rambling Rake Of Poverty, A Retrospect, Ruby Lips, Solomon, The Ship, Sage Maidens, Seventy-Five, Song Of The '83 Soph, Swing Low Sweet Chariot, Solomon Levi, Smoking Song, 'Tis A Way We Have At Cornell, There Thy Star Is Gleaming, Training Song, Two Little Co-eds, There's Music In The Air, When First We Saw The Major, The Way We Have At Cornell, Sir, The Winter, What Am The Song That I Do Sing, Ye Gallant Sophomore.
  - Cornell Songs (Songs of Cornell University), 1887 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Compiled by L. And H. Published by Andrus & Church. Only Authorized Edition. Second Edition. Notes that the work would not have happened without the assistance of C. B. Mandeville '77, F. A. Lorber '88, W. C. Kerr '79.
    Includes: Alma Mater, At Eight Upon The Hill, B. B. Club Song, B. & B., Bench And Board, Bonunkus, The Bold Fisherman, Boys Of The B&B, The Broken Chord, Bull-Dog, Cascadilla, Cayuga Boat Song, Chapeau, Children, Hail! Hail! Hail!, Ching Bum, The Chimes, Class Song '72, Class Song '73, Class Song '80, Class Song '83, Clementine, Cocachelunk, Cold Day When We Get Left, Cornell, Cornell's The Stuff, Crow Song, Days In Bivouac, Dip Me In The Golden Sea, Doloroso, Down In Old Kentucky, Drinking Song, Eighty-Three Song, Evening Song At Cornell, Friuja Club, Founder's Hymn, Fourteen Long Weeks In A Pris-i-on, The Girls Of Ithaca, Good Old Cornell Times, Gospel Train Am Coming, Hark, I Hear A Voice, Hard-Up, Hurrah, Hurrah, The Festival Hour Is Nigh, I Wish I Were Single Again, Jeremiah McGuire's Mare's Nest, Junior Exhibition, Junior Supper Song, Keep Me From Sinking Down, King Of The Cannibal Islands, Landlord, Fill Your Flowing Bowl, Leap Your Waltz Song, Litoria, Mary And Martha, Mermaid, Moustache, My Bonnie, My Little Dog, O'er Hill And Dale, Oh! Roger Ram, Once Was Enough For Me, Owl Song, Parting Song - Class Of '72, Rambling Rake Of Poverty, A Retrospect, Roll, Jordan, Roll, Ruby Lips, Sage Maidens, Seventy-Five, The Ship, Soldier's Farewell, Solomon, Solomon Levi, Song Of The '83 Sophomore, Smoking Song, Swing Low Sweet Chariot, Temptation, Tell Me Maiden, The Hour Is Late, There Thy Star Is Gleaming, There's Music In The Air, 'Tis A Way We Have At Cornell, Training Song, Two Little Co-eds, Upidee, Uralio, Way We Have At Cornell, Sir, We Are Camping To-Night, What Am The Song That I Do Sing, When First We Saw The Major, The Winter, Ye Gallant Sophomore.
  - Songs of Cornell, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Published by B. F. Lent.
    Includes: Alma Mater, Cornell, 1875 - The Cornell Cheer, The Chimes, Alumni Song, Song Of The Classes, Cornell Rowing Song, Crew Song, Bustonian Chorus, Cornell Boating Song, Big Red Team, Evening Song.
  - Cornell Chimes, 1901; 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Being an illustrated edition of Cornell songs. One copy is incomplete the other is printed on the back Annual dinner of the Cornell alumni association of Buffalo held at the Buffalo Club, February 21, 1901, the University will be represted by Professor H. Morese Stephens.
    Includes: Alma Mater, Cornell The Chimes, 1875, Alumni Song, Marching Thro' Cornell, The Classes, Bustonian Chorus, The Evening Song.
  - Cornell Chimes, ca. 1904 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Being a pocket edition of Cornell songs presented by the Ithaca merchants. Includes advertising for many local businesses.
    Includes: Alma Mater, The Chimes, Cornell Rowing Song, Alumni Song, Cornell, Busted, The Classes, Evening Song.
  - A Selection of Cornell Songs, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    To The Class of 1904. Includes advertising for many local businesses.
    Includes: Alma Mater, The Chimes, Cornell Rowing Song, 1875, Cornell, Marching Thro' Cornell, The Classes, Bingo, Evening Song, Busted.
  - Songs of Cornell, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Includes: Alma Mater, Cornell, 1875 - The Cornell Cheer, The Chimes, Alumni Song, Song Of The Classes, Cornell Rowing Song, Crew Song, Bustonian Chorus, Cornell Boating Song, Big Red Team, Fight For Cornell, Carnelian And White, Evening Song.
  - Songs of Cornell for Senior Singing 1914, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Edited by Anson L. Clark, Charles K. Bassett, and H. O. Underhill.
    Includes: Alma Mater, Alumni Song, Auld Lang Syne, Boola, Boola, Bye, Baby, Bye, Bring The Wagon Home, John, Bustonian Chorus, Carnellian And White, Crew Song, Cornell, Castle On The Nile, Cornell Rowing Song, Carry Me Back To Ole Virginia, Dat's Where Ma Money goes, Down Mobile, Dip Me In The Golden Sea, Dear Old Pals, Eli, Eveleine, Evening Song, Good-Bye Summer, Good Night, My Love, Good Night, Ladies, Give My Regards To Davy, Honey, Herpicide, I'm On My Way To Mandalay, In The Candle Light, I Want To Be 'Way Down In Dixie, Just A Song At Twilight, Jolly Boating Weather, Lord Geoffry Amherst, Lindy, Mary Jones, Old Man Noah, Oh, Ma Honey, Poughkeepsie Course, Stein Song, Sweet Adeline, Song Of The Classes, Senior, Junior, Sophomore, Frosh, There's A Girl In The Heart Of Maryland, The Big Red Team, Tennessee Moon, The Cornell Cheer, The Mermaid, The Chimes, Working On The Railroad, You're My Baby.
  - Cornell Songs, 1915; 5 copies (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Published by the Cornell Association of Class Secretaries. Contains information about the composers and dates of the songs.
    Includes: Alma Mater (1872) - Archibald Croswell Weeks '72 abd Willmot Moses Smith '74, Cornell (1869) - George Kingsley Birge '72, The Cornell Man (1907) - Kenneth Lewis Roberts '08 the Cornell Masque, The Cornell Cheer (1875) - John De Witt Warner '72, The Chimes at Fair Cornell (1891) - Fred Wallace Card '92, The Chimes (January 15, 1869) - Judge Francis Miles Finch written at the request of Jennie McGraw, Smoking Song (1870) - Judge Francis Miles Finch, Evening Song (1877) - Henry Tyrrell '80, Founder's Hymn (January 11, 1875) - Judge Francis Miles Finch, Founder's Centenary Hymn (January 11, 1907) - Burt Green Wilder, Rowing Song (1899) - Edward Ansell McCreary '00, Boating Song (1900) - William Allison Fuller '02, Regatta Song (Unknown), Crew Song (1897) - Robert James Kellogg '91, Cayuga Boat Song (1884) - Charles Babcock, The Big Red Team (1902) - Romeyn Berry '04, Carnelian And White (1908) - Kenneth Lewis Roberts '08, Cheer For The Team (1914) - Charles William Curtis '88 Rochester Cornell Club, Fight For Cornell (1906) - Kenneth Lewis Roberts '08, The Girls Of Ithaca (1880) - Harley Quinn, Sage Maidens (1880) - Charles Baker Mandeville '77, Tell Me, Maiden (1884) - Henry Tyrrell '80, Bustonia Chorus (1898) - Roland Franklyn Andrews '00, Song Of The Classes (1888) - Frank Addison Abbott '90, Freshman Song - On The Heights Above Cayuga (1873) - Stephen Perry Sturges '76, Junior Song - Ye Gallant Sophomore (1872) - Charles Fletcher Allen '73, Military Drill - When First We Saw The Major (1871) - John Bunyan Potter '74, At Eight Upon The Hill (Unknown), Cornell Club (Unknown), Give My Regards To Davy (Unknown), Senior, Junior, Sophomore, Frosh (Unknown), Alumni Song (1892) - Louis Carl Ehle '90, Cornell Celebrations (Celebration) (1914) - John Little Moffat '73, Reunion Song (December 29, 1914 - Henry Pelouze deForest '84, Cornellio (1885) - Elias David Abinun de Lima '86 Bench and Board, Class of '72 Song - The Ship Of Cornell (1870) - Albert Osborne '72, Class of '73 Song - Thy Bright Star Is Gleaming (June 16, 1873) - Charles Fletcher Allen '73, Class of '78 Song - Cornell Hymn (1906) - Albert William Smith '78, Class of '80 Song, Cayuga's Clustered Hills (June 15, 1880) - Henry Tyrrell '80, Class of '84 Song - The Cornell Grenadiers (June 22, 1904) Henry Pelouze de Forest '84 Twenty-Year Reunion, Class of '88 Song - Farewell Cornell (June 17, 1908) - Albert Ellis Hoyt '88 Twenty-Year Reunion, Class of '94 Song - Commencement Twenty Years After (June 12, 1914) - Herbert Latham Fordbam '94 Twenty-Year Reunion, Class of '05 Song - Glorious Mother - Cornell (June 17, 1908) - Robert Paul Butler '05 Three-Year Reunion.
  - Songs of Cornell for Senior Singing 1915, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Edited by Samuel H. Worrell. With introduction by Henry P. De Forest.
    Includes: Alma Mater, Alumni Song, Auld Lang Syne, Back To The Carolina You Love, Boola, Boola, Bye, Baby, Bye, Bring The Wagon Home, John, Bustonian Chorus, Celebratin' Day In Tennessee, Carnellian And White, Chinatown, My Chinatown, Crew Song, Cornell, Castle On The Nile, Cornell Rowing Song, Carry Me Back To Ole Virginia, Dat's Where Ma Money goes, Down Mobile, Dip Me In The Golden Sea, Dear Old Pals, Eli, Eveleine, Evening Song, Good-Bye Summer, Good Night, My Love, Good Night, Ladies, Good Bye Girls, I'm Through, Give My Regards To Davy, Honey, I Had A Dream, It's A Long Way To Tipperary, Just A Song At Twilight, Jolly Boating Weather, Jane, Lord Geoffry Amherst, Lindy, Old Man Noah, Oh, Ma Honey, Poughkeepsie Course, Roll Them Bones, Stein Song, Song Of The Cities, Sweet Adeline, Song Of The Classes, Senior, Junior, Sophomore, Frosh, The Big Red Team, Tip Top Tipperary Mary, The Cornell Cheer, The Mermaid, The Chimes, Working On The Railroad, You Wore A Tulip.
  - Songs of Cornell for Senior Singing 1916, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Edited by the Class of 1916.
    Includes: America, Alma Mater, Alumni Song, Auld Lang Syne, America, I Love You, Are You From Dixie, Bustonian Chorus, Boola, Boola, Bye, Baby, Bye, Bill Bailey, Bring The Wagon Home, John, Beach AT Waikiki, Carnellian And White, Carry Me Back To Ole Virginia, Cornell Victorious, Crew Song, Cornell, Castle On The Nile, Don't Go Away And Leave Me, Down Mobile, Dat's Where Ma Money goes, Dip Me In The Golden Sea, Eveleine, Evening Song, Eli, Give My Regards To Davy, Georgia Moon, Good-Night, Ladies, Honey, Hail Michigan, Here's To Old Cornell, I Had A Dream, Just A Song At Twilight, Jolly Boating Weather, Jane, Lindy, Lord Geoffry Amherst, Loading Up The Mandy Lee, Molly Dear, Old Man Noah, Oh, Ma Honey, On Christian Soldiers, Poughkeepsie Course, Push The Damper In, Roll Them Bones, Song Of The Cities, Stein Song, Song Of The Classes, Sweet Adeline, Senior, Junior, Sophomore, Frosh, The Big Red Team, The Mermaid, The Rocky Road To Dublin, The Cornell Cheer, The Old Green River, Working On The Railroad.
  - Songs - Cornell Semi-Centennial Celebration, 1919; 5 copies (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Published for events at the celebrations June 19-22, 1919.
    Includes: Alma Mater, Aloha Oe, Alumni Song, America, America The Beautiful, Annie Laurie, Auld Lang Syne, Battle Hym Of The Republic, Bring Back My Bonnie, Bostonian Chorus [sp], Carnelian And White, Caisson Song, Columbia, The Gem Of The Ocean, Come, Thou Almighty King, Cornell, Cornell Victorious, Cornell Will Shine Tonight, Crew Song, Dixie, Drink To Me Only With Thune Eyes, Eighteen Seventy-five, Evening Song, Faith Of Our Fathers, Fight For Cornell, Give My Regards To Davy, Good-night, Ladies, Good-night, My Love, Honey, How Firm A Foundation, I'm A Little Prairie Flower, I Need Thee Every Hour, I've Been Wukkin' On De Railroad, Jesus, Saviour, Pilot Me, Juanita, K-K-Katy, Keep The Home Fires Burning, Li'l Liza Jane, Lovely Evening, Love's Old Sweet Song, My Castle On The Sunny River Nile, My Moustache, Nearer, My God To Thee, Old Black Joe, Old Folks At Home, O God, Our Help In Ages Patt, Onward Christian Soldiers, Pack Up Your Troubles In Your Old Kit Bag, 'Round Her Neck She Wears A Yeller Ribbon, Row Your Boat, Semi-Centennial Song, Smiles, Song Of The Classes, Sweet Adeline, Sweet Genevieve, That Creole Gal O'Mine, That's Where My Money Goes, The Big, Red Team, The Bull-Dog, The Chimes, The Duke Of Yorkshire, The Little Brown Church, The Pope, The Quilting Party, The Sunshine Of Your Smile, The Star Spangled Banner, There's A Long, Long Trail, Till We Meet Again, Tulip And The Rose, We Meet Again Tonight, When I Survey The Wondrous Cross, When The Great Red Dawn Is Shining, Who Did?.
  - Cornell Songs, 1921 (Box 1)
    Published by the Women's Self-Government Association
    Includes: Alma Mater - Cornell, Song for Cornell, Loyal Daughters of Cornell, Cornell Victorious, Cornell, Carnelian and White, Fight for Cornell, All Round the World Cornell, Give My Regards to "Davy", Crew Song, The Big Red Team, Alumni Song, The Poughkeepsie Races, I Want To Go Back, Evening Song, The Chimes, Song of the Classes (Men), Song of the Classes (For the Girls), Rowing Song, Bostonian Chorus, I Want To Go Back To The Old Days, Old Man Noah, Down in Mobile, Moon, Moon; The Spanish Cavalier, Some Folks Hop Up and Down, Doggone That Moon, Alone, Tee-Hee, Alone; Wings, Down By The Stream, Sail, Seniors, Sail; Castle on the Nile, Auld Lang Syne, I've Been Working on the Railroad, I Want a Bungalow, Carry Me Back to Old Virginny, Father Time, That's Where My Money Goes, I Wish I Wuz a Little Rock, Sweet Evelyn, Toasts, Dear old Pals
  - Songs of Cornell, December 1922 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Fourth Printing. With foreword by Foster M. Coffin.
    Includes: Abdullah Bulbul Ameer, Ain't He Neat?, Alma Mater, Aloha Oe, Alumni Song, America, Annie Laurie, Auld Lang Syne, Away With Rum, Belinda, The Bells Of Hell, The Big Red Team, Boating Song, Bring Back My Bonnie, The Bull-Dog, Bustonian Chorus, Carnelian And White, The Chimes, Cornell, The Cornell Man, Cornell Victorious, Cornell Will Shine tonight, Crew Song, Dip Me In The Golden Sea, Dixie, Dreaming, The Duke of Yorkshire, Eighteen Seventy-Five, Evening Song, Everybody Works But Father, Faculty, Fight For Cornell, Give My Regards To Davy, Give Us A Drink, Bartender, Good-Night, Ladies, Here's To Old Cornell, Boys, Honey, I'm A Little Prairie Flower, Imogene Donahue, I've Been Workin' On De Railroad, I Want To Be A Barkeep, Juanita, Li'l Liza Jane, Lovely Evening, Love's Old Sweet Song, Mandy Lee, The Mermaid, Mobile, Mountain Dew, My Castle On The Sunny River Nile, Noah, Oh, My Honey, Old Black Joe, Old Folks At Home, Only A Sophomore, Poughkeepsie Course, 'Round Her Neck She Wears A Yeller Ribbon, Rowing Song, Row Your Boat, Song For Cornell, Song Of The Classes, The Star-Spangled Banner, Stein Song, The Sunshine Of Your Smile, Sweet Adeline, That Creole Gal O' Mine, That's Where My Money Goes, There's A Long, Long Trail, Till We Meet Again, Way Down Yonder In The Cornfield, We'll Have Just One More, We Meet Again Tonight, What You Going To Do When You Bust?, Who Did?, Yip-I-Add-I-Ay.
  - Songs of Cornell, December 1923 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Fifth Printing. With foreword by Foster M. Coffin.
    Includes: Abdullah Bulbul Ameer, Ain't He Neat?, Alma Mater, Aloha Oe, Alumni Song, America, Annie Laurie, Auld Lang Syne, Away With Rum, Belinda, The Bells Of Hell, The Big Red Team, Boating Song, Bring Back My Bonnie, The Bull-Dog, Bustonian Chorus, Carnelian And White, The Chimes, Cornell, The Cornell Man, Cornell Victorious, Cornell Will Shine Tonight, Crew Song, Dip Me In The Golden Sea, Dixie, Dreaming, The Duke of Yorkshire, Eighteen Seventy-Five, Evening Song, Everybody Works But Father, Faculty, Fight For Cornell, Give My Regards To Davy, Give Us A Drink, Bartender, Good-Night, Ladies, Here's To Old Cornell, Boys, Honey, I'm A Little Prairie Flower, Imogene Donahue, I've Been Workin' On De Railroad, I Want To Be A Barkeep, Juanita, Li'l Liza Jane, Lovely Evening, Love's Old Sweet Song, Mandy Lee, The Mermaid, Mobile, Mountain Dew, My Castle On The Sunny River Nile, Noah, Oh, My Honey, Old Black Joe, Old Folks At Home, Only A Sophomore, Poughkeepsie Course, 'Round Her Neck She Wears A Yeller Ribbon, Rowing Song, Row Your Boat, Song For Cornell, Song Of The Classes, The Star-Spangled Banner, Stein Song, The Sunshine Of Your Smile, Sweet Adeline, That Creole Gal O' Mine, That's Where My Money Goes, There's A Long, Long Trail, Till We Meet Again, Way Down Yonder In The Cornfield, We'll Have Just One More, We Meet Again Tonight, What You Going To Do When You Bust?, Who Did?, Yip-I-Add-I-Ay.
  - Songs of Cornell, January 1925; 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Sixth Printing. With foreword by Foster M. Coffin.
  - Songs of Cornell, January 1926 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Seventh Printing. With foreword by Foster M. Coffin.
  - Songs of Cornell, October 1930 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Ninth Printing. With foreword by Foster M. Coffin.
    Includes: Abdullah Bulbul Ameer, Ain't He Neat?, Alma Mater, Aloha Oe, Alumni Song, America, Annie Laurie, Auld Lang Syne, Away With Rum, The Bells Of Hell, The Big Red Team, Boating Song, Bring Back My Bonnie, Bring The Wagon Home, John, The Bull-Dog, Bustonian Chorus, Carnelian And White, Carry Me Back To Old Virgininy [sp], The Chimes, Chiming Bells, Cornell, The Cornell Man, Cornell Victorious, Cornell Will Shine Tonight, Crew Song, Dip Me In The Golden Sea, Dixie, Dolly Gray, Dreaming, The Duke of Yorkshire, Eighteen Seventy-Five, Eveline, Evening Song, Everybody Works But Father, Faculty, Fight For Cornell, Give My Regards To Davy, Give Us A Drink, Bartender, Goodnight, Ladies, Here's To Old Cornell, Boys, Honey, Imogene Donahue, I'm A Little Prairie Flower, I've Been Workin' On De Railroad, I Want To Be A Barkeep, Juanita, Li'l Liza Jane, Lindy, Lovely Evening, Love's Old Sweet Song, Loyal Daughters Of Cornell, Mandy Lee, The Mermaid, Mobile, Mountain Dew, My Castle On The Sunny River Nile, Noah, Old Black Joe, Old Folks At Home, Only A Sophomore, Poughkeepsie Course, 'Round Her Neck She Wears A Yeller Ribbon, Row Your Boat, Song For Cornell, Song Of The Classes, Song Of The Classes (Women), The Star-Spangled Banner, Stein Song, The Sunshine Of Your Smile, Sweet Adeline, That Creole Gal O' Mine, That's Where My Money Goes, There's A Long, Long Trail, There Was A Little Chicken, Till We Meet Again, Way Down Yonder In The Cornfield, We Meet Again Tonight, What You Going To Do When You Bust?, Who Did?, Yip-I-Add-I-Ay.
  - Songs of Cornell, October 1933; 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Tenth Printing. With foreword by Foster M. Coffin.
    Includes: Abdullah Bulbul Ameer, Ain't He Neat?, Alma Mater, Aloha Oe, Alumni Song, America, Annie Laurie, Auld Lang Syne, Away With Rum, The Bells Of Hell, The Big Red Team, Boating Song, Bring Back My Bonnie, Bring The Wagon Home, John, The Bull-Dog, Bustonian Chorus, Carnelian And White, Carry Me Back To Old Virgininy, The Chimes, Chiming Bells, Cornell, The Cornell Man, Cornell, Our Mother Dear, Cornell Victorious, Cornell, We Sing Thy Praise, Cornell Will Shine Tonight, Crew Song, Dip Me In The Golden Sea, Dixie, Dolly Gray, Dreaming, The Duke of Yorkshire, Eighteen Seventy-Five, Eveline, Evening Song, Everybody Works But Father, Faculty, Fight For Cornell, Give My Regards To Davy, Give Us A Drink, Bartender, Goodnight, Ladies, Here's To Old Cornell, Boys, Hail Thou In Majesty, Cornell, Hail To Thee, Our Alma Mater, The Hill, Honey, Imogene Donahue, I'm A Little Prairie Flower, I've Been Workin' On De Railroad, I Want To Be A Barkeep, Juanita, Li'l Liza Jane, Lindy, Lovely Evening, Love's Old Sweet Song, Loyal Daughters Of Cornell, Mandy Lee, The Mermaid, Mobile, Mountain Dew, My Castle On The Sunny River Nile, Old Black Joe, Old Folks At Home, Old Man Noah, Only A Sophomore, Poughkeepsie Course, Reunion Song (Women), 'Round Her Neck She Wears A Yeller Ribbon, Row Your Boat, Rowing Song, Song For Cornell, Song Of The Classes, Song Of The Classes (Women), The Star-Spangled Banner, Stein Song, The Sunshine Of Your Smile, Sweet Adeline, That Creole Gal O' Mine, That's Where My Money Goes, There's A Long, Long Trail, There Was A Little Chicken, Till We Meet Again, Way Down Yonder In The Cornfield, We Meet Again Tonight, What You Going To Do When You Bust?, Who Did?, Yip-I-Add-I-Ay.
  - Songs The '09 Class of Cornell Used to Sing and Still Do, June 1964 (Box 1)
    Collected and printed for their fifty-fifth reunion.
  - Cornell 1952 Sings, January 28, 1989; 2 copies (Box 1)
    Lion's Rock, 316 East 77th Street, New York, NY
    Includes: Selections reproduced from Songs of Cornell 1988.
  - Cornell Songs, ca. 1990; 3 copies (Box 1, Folder 3)
    An Alumni Affairs publication sponsored by the Cornell Association of Class Officers.
    Includes: Alma Mater, Alumni Song, The Big Red Team, Carnelian And White, Cornell, Cornell Hymn, Cornell Victorious, Crew Song, 1875, Evening Song, Fight For Cornell, Give My Regards To Davy, Hail Thou In Majesty, Cornell, The Hill, In The Red And The White, March On, Cornell, My Old Cornell, Song For Cornell, Song Of The Classes, Strike Up A Song To Cornell.
- Series IV. Miscellaneous Lyric Sheets and Music Related Items
  - Alma Mater or Cornell Hymn, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Lyrics by Archibald C. Weeks '72.
  - Beat Pennsylvania: Football Rally Program, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    No music, just lyrics. From a Tuesday night, November 27 rally at Bailey Hall.
    Includes: The Big Red Team, Fight for Cornell, Carnelian and White, Cornell Victorious.
  - Community Song Sheet, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Includes: America, Our Empire State, Let The Rest Of The World Go By, Long, Long Trail, Auld Lang Syne, Swanee River, America The Beautiful, Sailing, The Mummy Song, Sweet Adeline, 'Till We Eat Again, Pack Up Your Troubles In Your Old Kit Bag, Levee Song, School Days, Smiles, The Old Grey Mare, 'Round Her Neck She Wears A Yeller Ribbon, Round: - When You Meet A Donkey, Jingle Bells, Battle Hymn Of The Republic, Yawnin In The Mawnin, We're Here For Fun, Our Boys Will Shine, The Old Apple Pipe, The Damper Song, Carry Me Back To Old Virginny, Down In De Cornfield, Annie Laurie, Maggie, Dunderback, There Ain't No Flies On Us, In The Good Old Summer Time, The More We Are Together, Pussy Willow Song, Old MacDonald Had A Far, Our Cow, Style All The While, Chew-Chew, Paving, Moonlight And Roses.
  - Cornell College Songs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Appears to be published by the Cornell Glee Club. No music, just lyrics.
    Includes: The Chimes, Cornell, Alma Mater, The Winter, Hark; I Hear A Voice, I love My Love, Moustache, The Old Cabin Home, Smoking Song, Bingo, All Together, Landlord, Fill Your Flowing Bowl, Solomon Levi, Rumsty Ho!, What Am The Song What I Do Sing, Hard Up.
  - The Cornell March, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    No music, just lyrics.
    Also includes: There's Music In The Air, Landlord, Fill Your Flowing Bowl, 'Twas Oft The Blue Canaries, I've A Jolly Sixpence, 'Tis A Way We Have At Cornell, Cornell
  - Cornell Songs, Various; 7 versions (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Various pieces all titled Cornell Songs, none have music, just lyrics.